The Orrin E. Dunlap Collection
Niagara Falls Public Library
The Orrin E. Dunlap Collection
1861-1953
The collection includes: photographs, glass plate negatives, prints, books, paintings, manuscripts, pamphlets, documents, letters, typescripts, postcards, newspapers, scrapbooks and other materials representing one of the finest and most complete records of the history off the Falls of Niagara and its area. The photographs Dunlap took between 1890 and the 1920s are unique in the record they provide of the very important history of this region.
Dunlap, Orrin E., 1861-1953
Niagara Falls Public Library Local History Department 1425 Main Street Niagara Falls, NY 14305
None
Orrin E. Dunlap (1861-1953) was a photographer and writer based in Niagara Falls who offered a unique perspective on Niagara Falls. Dunlap was also the managing editor for the Niagara Falls Gazette from 1890-1895.
Dunlap, Orrin E. (Orrin Elmer), 1896-1970; Railroads--History.; State Reservation at Niagara (N.Y.); Niagara Falls (N.Y.); Niagara Falls (N.Y.)--Buildings, Structures, etc.--Pictorial works.; Black-and-white photographs; Color prints (photographs); Glass plate negatives; Manuscripts; Stunt performers; Women stunt performers; Photographers; Writers; Niagara Falls (N.Y.)--History.
The collection includes: photographs, glass plate negatives, prints, books, paintings, manuscripts, pamphlets, documents, letters, typescripts, postcards, newspapers, scrapbooks and other materials representing one of the finest and most complete records of the history off the Falls of Niagara and its area. The photographs Dunlap took between 1890 and the 1920s are unique in the record they provide of the very important history of this region.
- Box 199, 1910
- Box 201, 1870 - 1965
- Dunlap Articles Binder, 1898 - 1953
- 1870-1953
- Photographs, 1876 - 1933
- Glass Plate Negatives, 1870-1953
- Scrapbooks, Children's Books, and Ephemera, 1884 - 1952
- Newspapers, 1890 - 1950
- Financial Information, 1860 - 1911
- Correspondence, 1913 - 1951